import moment from 'moment';

const m1 = moment([2016, 6, 1]);
const m2 = moment();
const diff = moment.duration(m2.diff(m1));

export default {
    personality: 'FlamencoGuitar',
    personalityId: 4,
    conversations: [
        {
            id: '1',
            parentId: '',
            question: `Is it possible to learn Flamenco guitar on a steel-string guitar? Will it sound right?`,
            answer:
                'Playing Flamenco style on a steel string guitar will be rather painful',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '2',
            parentId: '',
            question:
                'How to overcome the frustration while you are developing demanding techniques?',
            answer: `Be patient and try multiple techniques, just not sticking to one`,
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '3',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'What types of guitars are used for spanish music?',
            answer:
                'They can be broadly classified into two types, Spanish classic guitar, Flamenco guitar.',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'Are long nails necessary for flamenco guitar?',
            answer:
                "You can't use a pick to gain speed, since techniques require use of multiple fingers",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '5',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'What happens if I leave the guitar for two months?',
            answer:
                'You\'ll rust your skills',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '6',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'Which guitar to pick for playing flamenco?',
            answer:
                'If available, get cypress (most common for "flamenca blanca" guitars) and you\'ll need a plate (golpeador) ',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '7',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'Have you tried Electric guitar for flamenco?',
            answer: "I don't own a electric guitar so I guess not!",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '8',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'What is the best way to learn Alzapua?',
            answer:
                'Try mastering base note, upward and downward stroke, and play with your wrist.',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '9',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'Which guitar do you have?',
            answer: 'I have an Ibanez classical guitar for now',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '10',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'Which classical guitar would you recommend to buy?',
            answer:
                "That's a very broad question, but I would say go for Ortega guitars",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '11',
            parentId: '',
            question: 'From where did you learn guitar techniques?',
            answer: 'I have subscribed to some of the online courses',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '12',
            parentId: '',
            question:
                'Did you ever break your nails, what did you do after that?',
            answer: 'I waited for my nails to grow up',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '1-1',
            parentId: '1',
            question: 'Have you tried that before?',
            answer: "No..., and I won't ever try it",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '2-1',
            parentId: '1',
            question: 'How is it painful?',
            answer:
                "Unless you have fists of Superman, you're gonna cut off your hands",
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-1',
            parentId: '1',
            question: 'I like the sound of steel string guitars',
            answer: "You're hopeless",
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '4-1',
            parentId: '1',
            question: "I don't agree",
            answer: "You're a noob",
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '1-2',
            parentId: '2',
            question: "I think I'll follow your advice",
            answer: 'Yea, you should',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '2-2',
            parentId: '2',
            question: 'What if I suck at multiple techniques too?',
            answer: 'That just means you suck',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-2',
            parentId: '2',
            question: 'I like to stick to one technique at a time',
            answer: 'Then it would take you years to overcome the challenge',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '4-2',
            parentId: '2',
            question: 'I get easily frustrated',
            answer: 'Trying doing some meditation and yoga',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '1-3',
            parentId: '3',
            question: 'What about steel string guitar?',
            answer:
                'What about them, you can\'t practice on that..',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '2-3',
            parentId: '3',
            question:
                'Where to get them?',
            answer: 'Fly to spain, lol....!',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-3',
            parentId: '3',
            question: 'There are many other types I suppose',
            answer:
                'The others can be classified to the subcategories',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-3',
            parentId: '3',
            question: 'I don\'t like flamenco music',
            answer: 'What are you doing here then, go away....',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },

        {
            id: '1-4',
            parentId: '4',
            question: 'My speed with the pick is much higher',
            answer:
                "We'll you are not close enough to match any professional flamenco players",
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '2-4',
            parentId: '4',
            question: "How can I switch from pick to fingers, It's too hard",
            answer: 'Patience from Zhou...',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-4',
            parentId: '4',
            question: 'Is there any other workaround for that?',
            answer:
                'You can try to guard your fingers with the protectors that are available in the market',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-4',
            parentId: '4',
            question: 'My girlfriend dumped me because I had long nails',
            answer: "Find a better life partner",
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '1-5',
            parentId: '5',
            question: "2 months is not a long time I suppose",
            answer: 'If you\'re quick on catching up then its not',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '2-5',
            parentId: '5',
            question:
                'I haven\'t played for a long time',
            answer: 'You should start today then',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '3-5',
            parentId: '5',
            question: 'Where do you get the motivation?',
            answer:
                'Watch some cool techniques and then try to replicate them',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-5',
            parentId: '5',
            question: 'I did that once',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '1-6',
            parentId: '6',
            question: "I didn\'t understand what you just said",
            answer: 'Google it!',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '2-6',
            parentId: '6',
            question: "What if I don\'t get the plate",
            answer:
                "Then you\'ll damage your guitar",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '3-6',
            parentId: '6',
            question: 'What if I don\'t buy a flamenco guitar and play on classical guitar',
            answer:
                'It\'ll damage your guitar',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-6',
            parentId: '6',
            question: "I don\'t have enough money to buy guitar",
            answer: 'Do some fundraising or sell lemonade on the streets',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '1-7',
            parentId: '7',
            question: "I tried it, it was good",
            answer: 'I haven\'t tried it but I know that you won\'t get that quality of the sound',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '2-7',
            parentId: '7',
            question: 'I suppose Flamenco on electric guitar sucks',
            answer: 'You\'re right!',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-7',
            parentId: '7',
            question: 'You should try it',
            answer:
                'Never....',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '4-7',
            parentId: '7',
            question: "I guess it would\'nt sound so bad",
            answer: "Try it at your own risk",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '1-8',
            parentId: '8',
            question: "You make it sound like it\'s easy",
            answer: 'Practice harder noob...!',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '2-8',
            parentId: '8',
            question: 'That\'s easy!',
            answer: 'Then try it!',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '3-8',
            parentId: '8',
            question: "Is there any other way?",
            answer: 'I am not sure, try searching for it',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-8',
            parentId: '8',
            question: 'I think you\'re guiding me the wrong way',
            answer: 'You\'re a noob',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '1-9',
            parentId: '9',
            question: 'That\'s a good guitar',
            answer:
                'Thanks....!',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '2-9',
            parentId: '9',
            question: 'Never heard about Ibanez',
            answer: 'No wonder, you girlfriend dumped you',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '3-9',
            parentId: '9',
            question: 'How much did it cost you?',
            answer:
                'My left Kidney...!',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '4-9',
            parentId: '9',
            question: "Ibanez is a great brand",
            answer: "Yes",
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '1-10',
            parentId: '10',
            question: 'Never heard of them in my entire life',
            answer:
                'Wow, your ignorance level is too damn high',
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '2-10',
            parentId: '10',
            question: 'What are Ortega guitars?',
            answer: 'They specialize in making classical and flamenco guitars, check their website',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '3-10',
            parentId: '10',
            question: 'Where are the Ortega guitars native in?',
            answer:
                "They are handcrafted and native in Spain",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-10',
            parentId: '10',
            question:
                'Ortega guitars cost too much',
            answer: 'Yes, absolutely!',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '1-11',
            parentId: '11',
            question: 'What are the various online courses that you\'ve subscribed to',
            answer:
                "Kelly Valleau, Thomas Zwijsen and Beyond The Guitar",
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '2-11',
            parentId: '11',
            question: 'It is hard to practice looking through the screen',
            answer:
                'You also need to have talent for that',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-11',
            parentId: '11',
            question: 'Online courses are worst',
            answer: "That\'s what she said, to you",
            mood: 'angry',
            sound: 'angry',
        },
        {
            id: '4-11',
            parentId: '11',
            question: "Is it better to get a tutor rather than online course?",
            answer: 'Yes, getting a tutor is much more helpful',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '1-12',
            parentId: '12',
            question: 'That\'s a lot of dedication',
            answer: 'Thanks!',
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '2-12',
            parentId: '12',
            question: 'That\'s hilarious',
            answer: "It is funny...",
            mood: 'happy',
            sound: 'happy',
        },
        {
            id: '3-12',
            parentId: '12',
            question: 'Did\'nt you try artificial nails?',
            answer: 'No, they are just as bad',
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
        {
            id: '4-12',
            parentId: '12',
            question: 'You should take care of nails more',
            answer: "I don\'t know",
            mood: 'normal',
            sound: 'okay',
        },
    ],
};
